MATEUSZ NIEDBAŁ

Junior Java Developer

& + 48 515 344 571

™ mat.niedbal@gmail.com

(ready to relocate)

http://mrndesign.eu/

Skills

- Programming Junior Skills: JAVA 8 and above, Android, Spring, Hibernate, MySQL, SQLite, HTML5, ThymeLeaf, REST, Mongo DB, CSS, JavaScript
- Programming tools:
 Intellij, Android Studio, GIT,
 Maven, Gradle, Rabbit, Postman;
- Programming Basics:
 C++, C#, PHP;
- Graphics: 3D MAX, Photoshop;
- OS I work on: Windows, Ubuntu;
- Soft skills: ability to work under the time pressure, involvement, conscientiousness, creative problem solving, team work, quick knowledge taker;



Foreign languages

- ➤ English B2/C1
- ➤ German A1/A2

Wyrażam zgodę na przetwarzanie moich danych osobowych dla potrzeb niezbędnych do realizacji procesu rekrutacji (zgodnie z ustawą z dnia 10 maja 2018 roku o ochronie danych osobowych (Dz. Ustaw z 2018, poz. 1000) oraz zgodnie z Rozporządzeniem Parlamentu Europejskiego i Rady (UE) 2016/679 z dnia 27 kwietnia 2016 r. w sprawie ochrony osób fizycznych w związku z przetwarzaniem danych osobowych i w sprawie swobodnego przepływu takich danych oraz uchylenia dyrektywy 95/46/WE (RODO).

About me

I am **ambitious** and **highly motivated** to start a career in IT field prepared for internship and/or remote/ full time work. My goal is to be a **valuable team member** in a **long - term collaboration** that has a real impact in creating software which provides innovative solutions for clients and company. Others describe me as a **flexible** person - easy to adapt to a new situation.

I am hard working with a positive attitude and willingness to learn and to gain experience. I find myself as a quick knowledge taker and creative person with a hint of empathy. I am open to support other fields according to my experience in a design, production and customer service. I am guided by the attitude that nothing is impossible.

Education

10/2019 – 18/09/2020 - Software Development Academy, Java from scratch (400 h – every weekend, excl. statutory holidays)

Programming course, focused around:

Java programming language & technologies involved:

Java, TDD, Maven, GIT, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, SQL, JDBC, Hibernate, JSP, Servlets, spring, Scrum.

Resulting repository of **projects**

Link: https://github.com/matned666?tab=repositories

My final project: https://the-final-project.herokuapp.com/

2006 - 2008 - College of Arts and Design, Łódź, Poland

Commercial photography, Advertisement, Modern media (not finished, 1,5 y./ 2y., due to work in the Netherlands).

2002 - 2005 - AFA, Wroclaw, Poland Artistic photography college

Modern media – digital photography, reportage,

Photoshop, Drawing, Painting

Resulting a group vernissage of diploma works

Link: http://artpicture.home.pl

1998 – 2002 - High school no. XX in Wroclaw, profiled – computer science

Resulting a basics knowledge of C++, Turbo Pascal

Courses

- Android from scratch, online programming apps course (20 h)

Resulting an some own projects

Link: https://github.com/matniedbal/First android app

Other 100% own android project:

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=pl.design.mrn.matned.dogmanagementapp

- Other online courses: Spring, SQL, SQLite, Hibernate, Security, Azure

Experience

02/2012 – now Manufacture MRN http://manufacture-mrn.pl/ Member of the board

- Designing and crafting handmade furniture for restaurants and offices, customer service, web design, 3D visuals, technical draw, logistic.
- Work with international environment
- Self-made websites HTML, WordPress
- Project architecture from marketing, contact with client through design to production and finish
- CRM utility

Resulting significant projects of restaurants, offices and homes

from 2007 - Own artistic projects http://artpicture.home.pl/

Graphic design, photography, individual and group exhibitions all around the world.

05.2008 - 01.2012 Phillips Lightning - Netherlands - Order Picker

Added value: Cooperation with an international team in a corporate environment.

Interests

- Programming own applications development , design
- Fencing , Ken-Jitsu, European martial arts
- Arts and Crafts Photography, graphics, blacksmithing